In order to make Lianmaoshan more convenient, please first import the basic T-shape file and the female downward line VR virtual model with the hole window.
Then press the control key to activate the simulation, and place the T-shirt on the virtual model.
Select the transparent image to check if the costume fits.
Comparing to the virtual model, the shoulder line of the costume is too short for the loose style of the costume.
Press the control key and point the shoulder line of the front and back slices out along the slope, then press the right key.
Enter 60 mm in the moving distance spring.
Press the control key and point the shoulder line of the front and back slices out along the slope.
Since the shoulder length has been increased, the highest point of the sleeve should be lowered by 30 mm to match the modification.
Select the editor curve point tool, delete the point higher than the curve of the sleeve, and add two straight lines to draw a short straight line.
Since the curve of the sleeve is very smooth and smooth, please adjust the hemline of the body plate as well.
Please keep the corner of the corner as straight as possible, so that after the line is cut off, it will not form a sharp corner.
Select the front and middle lines.
In the menu on the right, select Merge, and merge the two front slices as a whole.
Use the same operation for the back slices.
Increase the bottom line to shorten the length of the costume.
Select the bottom line and select the inner line of the shoulder line in the menu on the right.
Enter 45 mm in the shoulder line and click OK.
Then press the right key on the inner line and select the cut seam in the menu to remove the body plate slices from the bottom.
Select the side bottom point and move it out 30 mm to widen the waist.
Move the middle line of the body plate down 30 mm.
Then select the editor curve point tool, change the straight line to a curve line.
Click on the line section and drag the curve point.
Please adjust the corner of the corner as straight as possible.
Because the straight line is bent, the number of creases will increase, and there will be more creases to be created.
Now you can see that the back middle line is too long, please move the bottom point up a little.
Adjust the curve point to make the curve change more roundly.
Repeat these steps until you see the bottom flat in the 3D window.
Please adjust the curve point to make the curve change more roundly.
Move the bottom point of the sleeve to the outside 15 mm to increase the chest of the front and back slices.
Remove unnecessary points for the seam.
Move the seam line to increase the length of the sleeve.
Due to the 3D grid, it may break when extending, please rearrange the plate and simulate.
The seam is too wide, use the length tool to change it.
Set the length to 280mm, choose BOSE in the direction, and start from the middle to the length of the two ends of the calculation.
Since we will cut a sleeve plate from the sleeve plate, we can make it longer.
Use the inner thread to create the cut line of the sleeve plate.
Then select the cut seam in the window and automatically create the seam line.
Click the point with the longer thread, then select the point with the shorter thread and click it with the right button, then select the right one in the menu, and then select the left or right one according to the need.
Then the upper and lower threads will have the same length.
Drag the selection box to narrow the plate.
Activate the simulation, the sleeve plate will become wider.
Freeze the sleeve plate to maintain the shape.
Adjust the sleeve to be longer.
Since the sleeve plate is frozen, you can drag the sleeve to adjust the wearing effect.
Reactivate the sleeve plate, activate the simulation.
Create a 500mm wide, 500mm high rectangular plate.
Then arrange it on the side of the model's head.
Change the shape type to flat, which will help us create a simpler hat plate.
Use the 3D plate tool to open the transparency preview.
Click the plate to draw the line according to the model's head curve.
Press the CTRL key to create the curve, then click the starting point to complete the closed shape.
Then select the 3D tool to edit the line, and select the cut in the menu in the right button.
Now select the cut in the menu and select the cut in the menu.
Remove unnecessary curve points, and change some straight lines to curve points to make the curve smoother.
Choose a clear line on one side of the model and check the length by using the property editor.
Then drag the line in the back of the hat to match the line at the bottom and the size of the previous measurement.
Then drag the line in the back of the hat to match the line at the previous measurement.
Please adjust the curve in the back according to the video.
In this version, there will not be too many folds in the sewing line position.
Then create a symmetrical plate.
Use the positioning ball tool to move the symmetrical plate to the other side of the head.
Then select the line sewing tool to create a sewing line.
Then select the free sewing tool, click the starting point along the moving mouse of the sewing line and then click on the end position.
Then press the Shift key on the vertical line to gradually create a multilevel sewing line in the same way. Please ensure that the sewing line is marked on the right.
If the hat looks too tight, you can move the points on the plate or adjust the line to increase the plate.
Adjust the angle to a right angle to ensure that the sewing line can be too smooth after sewing.
Press the Ctrl key to drag the top point of the hat along the line to change the length.
Adjust the hat curve according to the need.
We suggest that you try to choose the way of adjusting the point, not the whole line to change. This can ensure that you try to maintain the original curve effect.
Then drag the hat to the back of the virtual model and adjust the shape to the appropriate effect.
To remove the beautiful hat, just press the Ctrl key on the top of the virtual model and then press the Ctrl key to adjust the draw.
Then drag the hat to the right angle to ensure that the sewing line is neat.
To have a neat hat, remove its center line and press the Ctrl key to adjust the photo line.
Then press the Ctrl key to open the virtual model and then press the Ctrl key to adjust the figure pattern.
and click on the point where you want to draw the curve.
Select the front piece,
then in the menu on the right-hand side,
select the pocket from the outside.
Then cut the pocket from the pocket on the plate of the pocket.
Now we have a pocket plate that is automatically arranged on the outside of the original plate.
Then you can use a free sewing tool
or a line sewing tool to sew the pocket plate to the inner line.
In the drawing window,
find the Materials file,
then drag the knit cord,
cotton cord,
jersey fabric to the current fabric maker to use it.
Thank you.